ILR School Timothy Schmidle ADR Files /4227
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Timothy Schmidle ADR Files
1919-2001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Schmidle, Timothy
/4227
15 cubic feet
15 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8055526
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 07, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Dispute resolution (Law); Schmidle, Timothy P., 1953-; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8055526
- Local 3 (BORBA) Data 1999. (Box 1)
  - Borsa Case, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Borsa Faxes, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Data Set Restrictions: Borsa, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Scope and Contents
    Occupation and State
  - Data Computations: Borsa Macros, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Borsa 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Borsa, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Borba and Pettas: Data, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Borba 1999 Working Folder: SAS Programs and M And R Comparisons (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Borba L3 (M&R) Data, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Conference Call, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Borba Data, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Borba 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Borba Contents Procedure, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Borba Meetings Procedure, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Borba SAS Frequency Procedure, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Awareness and Process Survey, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Borba Pettas Narrative Text, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Borba Frequency Procedure, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ADR (Working folders) 1999. (Box 2)
  - ADR Reports 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ADR Reports 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    26th November 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    November 10th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    November 29th 2000
  - New York State Workmen's Compensation, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    October 9th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    May 1st 2000, May 4th 2000, May 8th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    June 20th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    July 7th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    September 15 2000- September 20 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    March 21st 2000- March 27th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    March 12th 2000- March 14th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    April 24th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    December 20th 1999
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    April 3rd 2000 to April 6th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ADR N 76, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    November 15 1999
  - ADR N 76, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    May 25 1999 (Bob, Ron)
  - ADR Evaluation, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - ADR Burgher, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - ILR ADR, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Tables Memos
  - ADR N 76, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    November 29th 1999
  - ADR N 76, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    December 10th 1999
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    January 10th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    January 17th 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    February 23rd 2000
  - ADR N 76, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    February 1st 2000
- ADR Material. (Box 3)
  - Dispute Results, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Comparison Sets (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Summary Compilation of tables, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Closed case comparisons, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - SAS Printouts, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - SAS Survey of insured workers, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - SAS Dispute and Lawyer Questions, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - SAS Distribution of claims, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - SAS Jourey Men and Apprentices, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - SAS Local 3, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- ADR Material. (Box 4)
  - L3 Dispute Results, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Pettis L3, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Benefits Analysis, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ADR13MG1 Directory, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - TTESTS Means, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - WC ADR (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Welger, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - WEGENER (WCB), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - WEGENER, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ADR L3/EESISP HISTORY, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Washington Survey, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ADR Working Folder, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ADR, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ADR M76, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Local 3 (BORBA) Seg 5, Seg 6. (Box 5)
  - Recorded and Renamed Value Sets, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - EESIP Analysis and data dump, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - SE66A, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - SEGMENT 6, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    ICD-9
  - Treatment and Payment codes (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - SEG 6, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    CPTS #5
  - Segment 6, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    CPT
  - Segment 6 Not Special to CPT-4, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Segment 6 CP4 By ADR, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Borba Segment 5, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- ADR (2000; Fall 1999) Data set creation / Selected SAS runs (current). (Box 6)
  - Bills SAS Programs 00and Output, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Using CPT and ICD-9 Codes (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Merges, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Pettis Merge, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Merge, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    November 2nd 1999
  - Creation Perm Data Sets Merges, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Multiple Claim ID Problem in data sets, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SAS Printouts October 1999- March 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - ADR Dropped Cases, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Pettas (Open and Closed), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - LU 6, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Logistic Regression Models, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - SAS Printouts, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    April
  - ADR Vs Control Group, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Means Frequency And Univariate on Data, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - State Excel Test, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- ADR Local 3. (Box 7)
  - ADR LO6, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Local 3 Log, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ADR LOG, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Local 3 Survey, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ADR Log, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Hard Copy- Software Instructions
  - Local 3 Survey Printout, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Local 3 Data Manual (Pettas), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Master Copy
  - Local 3, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Local 3, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Contract Forms
  - ADR Contacts, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Luz Copy, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - ADR Contacts (Origins), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - State Rules, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - PPD Proxy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - PDR L3, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - LOG, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Local 3 LOG, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Local 3 (BORBA). (Box 8)
  - SAS Printouts Folder1, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SAS Printouts Folder2, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SAS Printouts Folder3, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - SAS Printouts Folder4, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - SAS Printouts Folder 5, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SAS Printouts Folder 6, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - SAS Printouts Folder 7, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SAS Printouts Folder 8, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - SAS Printouts Folder 9, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - SAS Printouts Folder10, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SAS Printouts Folder 11, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- ADR. (Box 9)
  - WC ADR In Other States, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Original Copies
  - Working Folder, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - ADR CA Evaluations, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - ADR Worker Folder, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - New York States Workman's Compensation Forms, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - OLS Duplicate Copies, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - ADR Contra Group, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Copy#2
  - ADR Worker Folder#1, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - ADR Tables, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Distributed at Previous M76
  - ADR Working Folder, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - ADR Data Manual, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Local 3 M76, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - ADR M76 Rights, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - ADR Evaluation, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- ADR / ADR working folders. (Box 10)
  - Workers Compensation Board CRA, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Working Folder, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - WCB(MAIR), 2000 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - ADR MA, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - WC ULGR Costs, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - ADR CA, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - CORN Tables, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - ADR Laws And Regulations, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - RIGAS, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Negotiation Journal, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - EL Contract Projects, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - SAS Printouts, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - SAS Printouts, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    May 1st 1997- April 30 1998
  - SAS Printouts, 1998-1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    May 1st 1998-April 30th 1999
  - ADR Working Folders, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - ADR Working Folders, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- ADR Riverside South / Eastern Contractors / Bechtel / RMPL / ULICO. (Box 11)
  - ADR AGREEMENTS, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Riverside South ADR Survey, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Contra Group, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Matches (Control Group), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Claim Records Folder 1, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Claim Records Folder 2, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Survey Records, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - ADR Riverside Survey, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Duplicates
  - Eastern Contractors Survey, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - RMPG, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - ADR Riverside Project, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - ULICO Downey, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Riverside South M76, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - RMPG Contact Survey Data, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Riverside South Control Group, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    State Fund
  - ADR ECA Surveys Results, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Riverside Contract, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- ADR Material. (Box 12)
  - Project Level Data, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Workers Compensation Insurance ADR Program, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - ADR Article Reprints, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - OLS LOGIT Folder, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - ADR Survey, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - ADR Section 2 Growth, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Tables, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Temporary Tables, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - ADR M76, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Contract Comparisons, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - ADR, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - SAS Printouts, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    March 30th
  - Database Administration, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - ADR File, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correlations, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- ADR Material. (Box 13)
  - ADR Pilot Project Evaluation, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - MGBPS Costs 0430A, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Days Compotation's (SAB), 1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Petitas L3, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - L3 M6 3, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Local 3, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Local 3 Pettas (closed), 1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - ADR LAWS PEGS, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Barabara Deinhart, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - WC MRG, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - OLS LOG IT, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - ADR MA, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - ADR With other States, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Working Folder ADR, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Working Folder # 1 Tables, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Merge Descriptive Statistics Tests, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- ADR Material. (Box 14)
  - Segments, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Tom Wegner, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Decision and Award Data, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - ADR Tabamws Notes, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - ADR Surveys, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - ADR, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - ADR State Agency, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - WEGENER, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - LOG Excel Files, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Preliminary Comparisons L3 Data Sets, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - LOG, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - L3 SAS Survey, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Tests Means, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Tests Means Duplicate, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- ADR (2000) Data set creation 2 / Log / Weggner / OLS; Survey of Injured Workers in New York State, 1996; New York State Worker's Compensation Managed Care Pilot Project, 1997; Worker's Compensation Alternative Dispute Resolution Pilot Project. (Box 15)
  - YRBYYR Comparisons, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Data Restriction Rows, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Segment 6, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - MG04235E66 Data Set, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ADR OLS Runs, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The California Commission on Health and Safety and Workers Compensation, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - SAS Printouts, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Narrative Text, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - ADR Survey, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - ADR Websites, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Dissertation Coverage, 1974-1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Workers Compensation, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - MR Filename Printouts, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - ADR Survey, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - ADR Survey Without Riverside, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - ADR LOG Master Copy, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - ADR W6 Printouts Distribution Of Software, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - ADR Log (Older Version), 1997 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - ADR Log, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 19)